[Music]
look I'm Catholic so like most of you I
was raised to avoid the noise
right I was that's how I was raised in
my church and in my home we like our
pizza piping
hot but far be it for me to tell that
staffer that he can't bow to the altar
of his cold pizza guide because that's
what makes this nation
great right I think the good news says
I've been blessed with good health with
a lot of endurance if you could just do
this for me just in case Bernie could
you just put these sunglasses on just
absolutely thanks just in case we have
to do the weekend of Bernie thing how's
that that's awesome and just kind of go
like
this how's that that's fantastic when it
comes to the Kardashians it's like look
can we just make a deal you can keep all
the black hairstyles if you just give us
some of the black men
back I will take Lamar Odum I can fix
his crack problem it's not a big deal I
can fix
the New York Times reports that a
different study of the same Marine
showed that the female Marines scored
higher in mental resilience and had
fewer mental health problems so in other
words while men may be better at lifting
heavy with their arms women are better
dealing with heavy in their
brains there's going to be women that
are more qualified than men and men that
are more qualified than women I am not
qualified I am in no way shape or form
should I be that the only thing I would
have in
with a woman that's qualified for the
military is like my titties that's it
you can only save two of your cohorts
cohorts from Impractical Jokers okay uh
who do you save Joe Brian Quinn or James
Murray well I could save two two yeah
one has to go I guess right James Murray
is dying he's dying yeah I don't even
need to think about it real yes I'm I'm
keeping it like 500 million I get it
with the little Fiat you're the humble
Pope but I'm not sure you get full
humble points for your Fiat when it's
being traed by 100 blinged out security
SUVs and I'll be honest with you we're
American small doesn't impress us unless
a hundred other popes come out of that
theat
then then we're impressed be honest keep
it h 100 was it a little cool to be
arrested I mean it does give you a
little street cred back
here um it it was It was kind of
cool was nter n Twitter accounts with
with millions of followers that's why
I'm a little concerned the celebrity is
getting to his head because he he has
nine Twitter accounts with millions of
followers but he only follows eight
people it's true it's true guess who he
follows guess who he guess who he
follows his other Twitter
account one tablet of Derr used to cost
$13.50 the drug maker recently increased
the price to
$750 guys look I know exploiting AIDS
and cancer patients for profit sounds
like evil in its purest
form anyway
um it's 2015 don't you think it's time
the pope changes up his gear yeah man
you need to go get him a baseball hat or
something oh you can go put a daiki or
something on you know I mean I mean he
might look good in daiki oh you can go
get a Steve Harvey op or something I
don't know that' be tight I was in
Poland a couple years ago and a friend
of mine and I went
totz yeah and the tour Ends by going
into the gas Chambers and they show you
the gas chamber and these two girls and
I was like please don't let them be
American
Americans had the camera out trying to
smile taking the picture you have to be
no it's true and again I was like ask
someone else to take
it hey America follow the nightly show
with Larry Wilmore on Twitter but don't
follow me home I want followers but I
don't want followers
that's stalking